dealticker.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy

**Last Updated on October 18, 2010**

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how DealTicker collects information from all end users (“Users”) of DealTicker's Web site Services (the "Services"), what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such information. DealTicker requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Personal Information DealTicker Collects and How It Is Used**

**Introduction.** DealTicker collects information in different ways from users who access the various parts of our Services and the network of web sites accessible through our Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services. We do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.

**Registration.** Users are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, email address, billing information (such as a credit card number). The personal information collected from users during the registration process is used to manage each individual’s account (such as those used for security and billing purposes). This information is not shared with third parties unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. DealTicker may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Users provide during registration. No personally identifiable information will be disclosed to the public.). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregate and non-identifying information to further enhance our services.

**Disclosure of Personal Information.** It is DealTicker's policy not to use or share the personal information about its users. However, DealTicker may disclose personal information about Visitors or Customers, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, if you have expressly instructed us to do so or for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect DealTicker and our Customers.

**DealTicker Partners and Sponsors.** Some DealTicker products and services are offered to users in conjunction with a non-affiliated partner or sponsor. To provide users some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. DealTicker will share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered.

**Responses to Email Inquiries.** When Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to DealTicker, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. DealTicker does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

We may periodically conduct both business and user surveys. We encourage our users to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer Surveys and aggregate it to create broad, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregate information to improve the quality of our services, and to develop new services and products. This aggregate non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

**"Cookies" and How DealTicker Uses Them.** A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. DealTicker may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our networks. If you are a Member (an individual who has an active profile on DealTicker.com and/or DealTicker.us), we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Non-affiliated partner or sponsors may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

DealTicker recommends that children ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to DealTicker, or to anyone else online.

Please remember that any information you may disclose in public areas of our web sites or the Internet becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

**DealTicker's Commitment to Data Security.** Services and web sites we sponsor or host have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

**Where to Direct Questions About DealTicker’s Privacy Policy.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact: [info@dealticker.com](mailto:info@dealticker.com).

Customer Service  
DealTicker Inc.  
5000 Yonge St., Ste 1901  
Toronto ON M2N 7E9
